[
    {
        "question": "What node is used for generating a list of floating-point numbers within a specified range in ComfyUI?",
        "answer": "The CR Float Range List node is used for generating a list of floating-point numbers within a specified range in ComfyUI."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the `start` input in the CR Float Range List node?",
        "answer": "The `start` input in the CR Float Range List node defines the starting point of the float range and sets the initial value from which the sequence begins."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which input type is used to determine the density of the sequence generated by CR Float Range List?",
        "answer": "The `step` input type is used to determine the density of the sequence generated by CR Float Range List. It specifies the increment between each number in the range."
    },
    {
        "question": "How can the output of CR Float Range List be transformed using trigonometric functions?",
        "answer": "The output of CR Float Range List can be transformed using trigonometric functions by setting the `operation` input to 'sin', 'cos', or 'tan'."
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the `ignore_first_value` boolean input do in CR Float Range List?",
        "answer": "When the `ignore_first_value` boolean input is set to true, the CR Float Range List node omits the first value of the generated range from the output."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the role of the `max_values_per_loop` input in the CR Float Range List node?",
        "answer": "The `max_values_per_loop` input limits the number of values generated per loop in the CR Float Range List node, providing control over the size of the output list within each iteration."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of output does the CR Float Range List node generate?",
        "answer": "The CR Float Range List node generates a list of floating-point numbers within the specified range as a`FLOAT` output type."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which input allows the CR Float Range List node to repeat the range sequence?",
        "answer": "The `loops` input allows the CR Float Range List node to repeat the range sequence, indicating how many times the sequence should be repeated."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can the CR Float Range List node create a back-and-forth pattern in its output?",
        "answer": "Yes, the CR Float Range List node can create a back-and-forth pattern in its output by setting the `ping_pong` input to true, which reverses the direction of the range on every other iteration."
    },
    {
        "question": "What additional information can be found with the `show_help` output of the CR Float Range List node?",
        "answer": "The `show_help` output of the CR Float Range List node provides a URL to a help page that offers detailed information and guidance on using the CR Float Range List node."
    }
]